EREZ LEVY

054-3032603

Erez84Levy@gmail.com ✓



https:/www.linkedin.com/in/erez-levy-629b896a in

Born: 1984 #



OBJECTIVE

Over 9 years experiencing in leading SW qualification and releases of complex systems involving high scale of data and high performance. Getting involved with aspects impact the customers across the global, serving as focal for any issues and demands required as part of my support.



EDUCATION

B.A in business management and information systems | Ono Academy 2010 - 2013

Automation testing | The Automation College 2022



EXPERIENCE

QA Team lead | Nova Measuring instruments

2021 - PRESENT

• Managing 4 employees. • Managing tasks, the company's schedule. • 50% Hands on

Linux sysadmin in DevOps team | Nova Measuring instruments 2019 - 2021

Working mostly with CentOS • I was Installing BI and Cloudera systems. • Bash Scripts editing. • Writing docs like release notes, and installation guides. • Provide training for our global teams. • Managing the RND's VMware environment.

Senior QA team member | Nova Measuring instruments

2016 - 2019

Testing fronted Software systems. • Testing and leading new features and builds. • Documentation writing (STR/STD, Guides, and user manual), TP reviews.

QA team member and TAM | FRSVision

2013 - 2016

I was leading the whole process of testing and managing build for one of the company's biggest customers where I have also worked as the account manager.



SKILLS

- MS SQL server, MySQL, SQL queries, Windows servers, XMLs, Application and web servers.
- Selenium, Postman, RestAPI, Allure, Maven, Jenkins, Github.
- MTM, BugTrucker, TFS, QC

- Linux (CentOS), Bash, Cloudera, BI, Kafka, Hadoop-HDFS.
- VMware, Storage, Network devices, Firewall, Wireshark
- Languages: English and Hebrew fluent



MILITARY SERVE

2003 – 2006: IDF, Full Service, in charge of the Armory in the Base.